presentationhelper.co.uk 2017-03-14

# Privacy Policy

This page explains our approach to privacy and how it affects you.

**Short version**

We collect anonymous statistics about your visit, like which of our pages you viewed.  
Some third parties like Facebook and Twitter may know you visited this website, if you use their services. We can’t control them but we don’t believe this knowledge poses any threat to you.  
If you sign up with us we take great care to keep your information safe and we’ll never share it with others without your express permission.  
We never share your data with 3rd parties except to help us deliver our own services.

**Measuring our visitors**

We measure visitors to our website using Google Analytics. This records what pages you view within our site, how you arrived at our site and some basic information about your computer. All of that information is anonymous – so we don’t know who you are; just that somebody visited our site.

The information we collect from analytics helps us understand what parts of our sites are doing well, how people arrive at our site and so on. Like most websites, we use this information to make our website better.

You can learn more about Google Analytics or opt out if you wish.

**Facebook, Twitter and other social networks**

These services provide social buttons and similar features which we use on our website – such as the “Like” and “Tweet” buttons.

To do so we embed code that they provide and we do not control ourselves. To function their buttons generally know if you’re logged in; for example Facebook use this to say “x of your friends like this”. We do not have any access to that information, nor can we control how those networks use it.

Social networks therefore could know that you’re viewing this website, if you use their services (that isn’t to say they do, but their policies may change). As our website is remarkably inoffensive we imagine this is not a concern for most users.

**If you sign up for a service**

When you sign up for any of our services – paid or otherwise – we will record specific personal information about you, such as your name and email address.

We will also collect and store information about your use of our services so as to improve them. For example, we keep a log of what features are being used at any time.

We also log account and transaction history for accounting purposes, and to monitor our business activities.

**Emails**

We may send you email notifications regarding your service (such as invoices) or which you have specifically requested (such as newsletters). You have the ability to opt out of any of this communication at any time.

**Online payment**

We use companies like PayPal to bill for our products online. These companies will have access to your personal and payment information. When paying by credit card, we do not ever have any access to your credit card details.

The third parties we use are PayPal (to process credit cards and accept payment via PayPal).

We share information with these companies only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our website.

**Cookies**

We gather data in the form of cookies. Cookies are little bundles of information which are transferred and saved on the hard drive of your computer, which interacts with our site. This allows us to see your browsing on the site.

Call Centre Helper uses cookies to create a better experience when you are reading articles, and to optimise results when searching the website, as well as remembering your previous searches.  
We also use cookies to remember some information, such as your email address and name. This means when you are filling in forms for a second time on our site, it is quicker and easier.

If you don’t want to accept cookies you must use the settings on your internet browser to refuse the cookies. Without cookies, some of the services on the website will be limited and some of the functionality with be reduced.

**Security**

We take many precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. These precautions include:

Hardware stored in secured data centres behind firewalls.  
All access to information restricted by password and/or secure key.  
Restrictions to what information can be accessed via any location.

Whilst we take great care to ensure any confidential information remains protected we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the Internet.

**Updates to this policy**

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time, particularly as technology changes. You can always check this page for the latest version. We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.

Published On: 1st Jan 2015 

Read more about -
